‎NETFLIX アニメシリーズ
‎（ユミコ）エバンス所長
Director Evans.
‎（エバンス）
‎何だ！　なぜ黙って入ってきた
What? Where did you come from?
I'm sorry, sir. I did knock a few times…
‎（ユミコ）申し訳ありません
‎何度か お声がけを…
Fine, fine… What do you want?
‎（エバンス）
‎まあいい　用件は何だ？
Um… May I go home for the day?
‎（ユミコ）その…
‎お先に失礼しても
‎よろしいでしょうか
‎（エバンスのため息）
I'm sorry, sir.
I had plans for this evening…
‎（ユミコ）すみません
‎今日は予定がありまして
I hadn't realized that managing
your schedule was also my job.
‎（エバンス）私が君の予定を
‎管理しなければならないのかね？
N-No, sir. It's just…
‎あ いえ… 申し訳ありません
I wanted to celebrate
my son getting into the Academy…
‎でも 今日は息子の
‎アカデミーの合格祝いで
Oh! Well, that's wonderful. We all
look forward to another legacy hire.
‎それはそれは おめでとう
‎アラサカの未来の星だな
‎なら誰かに‎ＵＧ２(ユージーツー)‎のサンプルを
‎持ってこさせろ
Just find someone to fetch the UG2 sample.
‎ほかのスタッフは
‎定時で帰宅していて…
Everyone has already
gone home at this hour…
‎（ため息）
‎（ユミコ）
‎サンプルは私がお持ちします
I'll bring over the sample myself… so…
‎それで…
‎（エバンス）
‎これは ありがたい申し出だ
How very kind of you.
Fetch it and get out of my sight.
‎さっさと持ってきて とっとと帰れ
‎（戸棚を探る音）
Director Evans?
‎（ユミコ）エバンス所長？　あ…
‎（デイビッドの荒い息）
‎ひっ！
‎（箱が落ちた音）
‎（震える息）
Wait…
‎待って
‎（発砲音）
‎（物音）
‎（レベッカ）ん？
‎（キーウィ）さっきの何だったの？
What happened in there?
‎（デイビッド）
‎一瞬 聞こえづらくなった
Lost you for a sec.
Someone raise a jammer?
‎ジャミングか？
Transmission was stable.
‎（キーウィ）
‎通信は切れてなかったけど
‎（デイビッド）そうか
Weird.
‎（レベッカ）よっ あーあ
Yeesh, what a boring gig.
‎退屈な仕事だったの～
‎（エンジン始動音）
♪～
～♪
‎（ケイト）施設内で堂々と暗殺か
‎アラサカもナメられたものだな
They trespassed on Arasaka premises,
hit us in our own fucking facility.
‎（ダグラス）
‎ミリテク対策の研究室が
The lab's research focused
on Militech countermeasures.
‎狙われたようです
‎（ケイト）
‎ジェイミーやマーカスを‎殺(や)‎った
Is this related to the runner
who flatlined Jamie and Marcus?
‎ランナーとの関係性は？
Evans was murdered by a bullet…
‎（ダグラス）所長のエバンスは射殺
This was sloppy, violent.
Safe to say, not the same runner.
‎痕跡の消し方も少し雑でしたので
‎ランナーとは別線のようです
Apprehending the netrunner's our priority.
They're too dangerous.
‎（ケイト）
‎ランナーの特定が最優先だ
‎あいつは危険すぎる
But we know neither
their motive nor purpose…
‎（ダグラス）
‎しかし 動機も目的も不明
Whoever they are, they're cautious.
‎まるでシッポがつかめません
Not your average runner looking to score.
‎野良のランナーレベルじゃ
‎ありませんね
We're Arasaka Counterintel.
We never deal with average.
‎（ケイト）
‎我々 防諜部の手を焼かせるとは
We'll need to take a detour
to catch the runner's trail.
‎ランナーの痕跡を追うには
‎回り道が必要か
Are we going after Evans' killer?
‎（ダグラス）エバンスのほうを
‎探るつもりですか？
It's two separate roads.
We may get lucky and find that they merge.
‎（ケイト）別々の事件が
‎思わぬ足がかりになることもある
Let's switch it up.
We'll go after the fixer.
‎（ケイト）狙いを変えよう
‎アレンジしたフィクサーを探す
Who do we know that has ties to Militech?
‎ミリテクと縁の深いやつを絞るのは
‎そう難しくない
But if the fixer we get
has ties to the runner,
（ダグラス）しかし
フィクサーとランナーに
つながりがあった場合
they could turn around and leak info
about the product to Militech.
例のプロダクトに
関わる情報を
逆にミリテクに売られる
可能性があるのでは？
‎狡猾(こうかつ)‎さと保身術に‎長(た)‎けていなければ
They'd be a poor fixer
if they weren't a self-serving bastard.
‎ナイトシティで
‎フィクサーは名乗れない
But at the end of the day,
they're only glorified corporate lapdogs.
‎しかし しょせん
‎企業のおこぼれをもらうハイエナさ
We'll just remind them
whose hand they eat off of in this city.
‎企業が牛耳る この街では
‎飼い犬しか生きられないことを
‎教えてやるだけだ
How would you go about this?
‎どんな やり方で？
‎フッ 我々もナイトシティ流で
‎いこうじゃないか
We tell them
in the only language this city speaks.
‎（車の加速音）
‎（ファラデー）ん？
‎おい！
Hey…
‎（銃声）
‎（衝突音）
（タイガークロウズ）
フィクサーは殺すな！
Take the fixer! Kill the others!
ほかは殺していい
Grenade!
‎グレネードだ！
Go! Go!
‎投げ返して… ぐわっ！
‎（発砲音）
‎（ファラデー）殺されかけたんだぞ
I was very nearly killed.
What makes you think it was Arasaka?
‎（男）
‎アラサカの差し金とは限らないだろ
Do you take me for a fool?
Who else could it have been?
‎（ファラデー）
‎バカな　ほかに誰が俺を狙う？
We're not paying
for any additional liabilities.
‎（男）だからといって
‎追加資金は認められんよ
And corporate immunity
is still off the table.
‎訴追免責の件も難しいな
‎（ファラデー）冗談だろ
Are you serious?!
We're already in the red
with your slip-up on the Tanaka case.
‎（男）タナカの件の事後処理に
‎いくらかかったと思ってる？
‎しかも成果はなしだ
With nothing to show for it.
We expect returns on our investments.
‎君への追加投資が必要というなら
‎まずは結果を見せてもらわないと
Want more resources? Show us results.
And what the hell do you think
I've been chasing?
‎今までの働きでは
‎不服だと言いたいのか？
You're running out of time.
Our patience is running thin.
‎（男）そこまでは言わんが？
‎まあ 時間がかかり過ぎるとは
‎思うがね
Arasaka's security
is on higher alert than usual.
アラサカのガードが
尋常ではないからさ
Goes to show just how important
the cyberskeleton is to them.
それだけ
アラサカにとって
サイバースケルトンが
重要だという証拠だ
You expect too much.
分からんか？
（男）分かっているから
Don't lecture me on the stakes
with all the money we've invested in this.
ここまで
つぎ込んできたんだ
結果を出してくれ
Not another enny until you earn it.
We're done here.
成果なしに
増額はできんよ
話は以上だ
‎チッ… 末端の若造が
Damn corporate brat…
‎（ホロコール発信音）
The fixer's made contact.
‎（ダグラス）
‎例のフィクサーが接触してきました
‎（ケイト）狙いどおりだな
As I predicted.
What a good little dog.
‎腰の軽いハイエナだ
‎（テレビ音声）
‎（ルーシー）ん？
David?
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド？
Oh, my bad.
‎（デイビッド）あ… ああ　ごめん
‎起こしたかな
Did I wake you up?
‎（ルーシー）眠れないの？
Can't sleep?
‎（デイビッド）
‎なんか 目がさえちゃって
Couldn't shut my brain off.
‎（ルーシー）そう
‎（デイビッド）消すよ
Oh.
I'll turn it off.
Aren't you watching?
‎（ルーシー）見てるんでしょ？
No, I just had it on…
‎（デイビッド）
‎つけてるだけだから… あっ
Oh.
250K to the Moon…
Huh, cheaper than I thought.
‎月… 25万で行けるって
‎意外と安いと思わない？
For a one-way ticket.
‎行くだけならでしょ？
Well, yeah.
‎（デイビッド）まあ そうだけど
‎フッ… 覚えてんだ
You remembered…
Huh?
‎え？
Nothing. I'm going back to bed.
‎（ルーシー）ううん　もう寝るね
Okay. 'Night.
‎うん　おやすみ
‎世界一の日本企業の防諜部が
‎こんな所で密会か？
The world's greatest corporation
conducting illicit business at a diner.
I thought you'd find
the familiarity reassuring.
‎そちらの様式に
‎合わせているつもりだが
I won't pick hairs.
I'm here for your answer.
‎（ファラデー）
‎まあいい　返答を聞こう
‎（ダグラス）サイバースケルトンは
‎我がアラサカでも
The cyberskeleton project is
a delicate topic even within Arasaka.
‎デリケートなプロダクトだ
‎タナカに情報を
‎集約し過ぎていたことが
It turned problematic when Tanaka
over-consolidated the operational data.
‎裏目にも出ている
‎ミリテクは どこまで知っている？
How much does Militech already know?
Information is the blood of my trade.
‎（ファラデー）情報は命綱だ
‎先に保証の確約が欲しい
I'll need some assurances
before I say any more.
We respect that
you're the best man for the job.
‎我々は 君ほどのフィクサーは
‎いないと理解している
We'll gladly provide the compensation
Militech foolishly denied you.
‎ミリテクが断った君の条件は
‎全面的にのもう
As for the Tanaka mess,
consider your debt settled.
‎タナカの拉致についての
‎恩赦も同じだ
Wonderful.
‎すばらしい
However, we have some conditions as well.
‎しかし こちらにも条件がある
Let's hear it.
‎聞こう
‎サイバースケルトンの存在を
‎知っている者を
We need to eliminate anyone
who knows about the cyberskeleton.
‎全員 始末すること
Done.
‎（ファラデー）問題ない
And one more thing.
‎もう１つ聞きたい
Yes?
‎（ファラデー）何だ
After Tanaka died,
‎タナカが死んだあと
there's been a runner interfering
with our recovery on the corrupt data.
‎破損した
‎サイバースケルトンに関する
‎データの復元を
‎妨害するランナーがいる
‎それについて何か情報は？
Know anything about it?
Not that I can recall.
‎知らんな
I see.
‎（ダグラス）そうか
‎これに関しては謎が多くてね
We're quite curious about this case.
Even if this were Militech,
I can't even imagine why they'd do this.
‎そもそもミリテク側の
‎オーダーだとしても
‎何が目的なのか分からない
From what my sources tell me,
‎タナカがサイバースケルトンに
‎関与しているとつかんでいるのは
no one else knows about Tanaka's ties
to the cyberskeleton project.
‎私以外には考えられない…
‎内部では？
An inside job?
‎ありえない
No. It's impossible to move internally
without leaving a trail.
‎内部から痕跡を残さず
‎動き回るのは不可能だ
‎腕利きのランナーが
‎サイバーパンク‎界隈(かいわい)‎に——
It's more natural to think that
it's a skilled runner from the outside.
‎潜伏していると考えるほうが自然だ
Seems to me like a job for a fixer.
‎フィクサーである君の分野だろう
Is this an official commission?
‎それは追加依頼だな？
One million to take them alive.
Half the price for their head.
‎生きたまま
‎引き渡してくれたら100万
‎死体でも50万出そう
I accept.
‎引き受けよう
‎（ホロ通信：キーウィ）‎あんたから
‎連絡くれるなんて珍しいね
‎（ルーシー）‎久しぶり
‎（キーウィ）‎どうかした？
‎（ルーシー）
‎うん 少し聞きたいことがあって
‎（キーウィ）‎何かしら？
‎（ルーシー）‎大したことじゃないの
‎デイビッド
‎うまくやってるかなって
‎（キーウィ）‎よくやってると思うよ
‎最初はサポートしてあげるつもりで
‎組んでたけど
‎今じゃ普通にリーダーって感じ
‎ファラデーからも
‎仕事の依頼が来るようになったし
‎（ルーシー）‎みたいね
‎（キーウィ）‎今のデイビッドを
‎メインが見たら 驚くでしょうね
‎（ルーシー）‎へえ
‎（キーウィ）
‎何か心配なことでもあるの？
‎（ルーシー）
‎別にそういうわけじゃ…
‎ちゃんとやれてるなら
（キーウィ）
一緒に仕事してみれば？
（ルーシー）え？
‎（キーウィ）‎デイビッドは
‎あんたが その気になるまで
‎待つつもりみたいだけど
‎ホントは すぐに
‎戻ってほしいと思ってるよ
‎（ルーシー）‎分かってる
‎（キーウィ）‎まだ無理なの？
‎（ルーシー）‎今は まだ… ね
‎でも もうすぐ終わりそうだから
‎（キーウィ）‎ふーん
‎まっ 詮索はしないよ
‎ナイトシティでは人を信じるな
‎信じてダマされたほうが悪いって
‎昔 教えたもんね
‎（ルーシー）‎フッ 言ってたね
‎（キーウィ）‎まあ 早く
‎戻ってきてくれるのを待ってるわ
‎デイビッド ちっとも
‎言うこと聞かないしね
‎（ルーシー）‎何それ フフッ
‎じゃ また
‎（通信切断音）
‎（玄関チャイム）
‎（ホロ通信：ファラデー）‎私だ
‎（ため息）
‎（アニマルズ）うおーっ！
‎うおーっ！
‎（高笑い）
‎（レベッカ）
‎ミチミチのミンチやで これ！
Take that!
‎（レベッカ）弾切れ！
‎（デイビッド）了解
Out of juice!
Gotcha.
‎（アニマルズ）う… うう…
‎ひいっ！
‎ううう…
‎待って
‎ハッ…
‎（発砲音）
What are you doing?!
‎何やってんの！
Ah… My bad.
‎ああ　悪い
‎（ファルコ）じゃあな デイビッド
‎（デイビッド）ああ
Later, David.
Yeah…
‎ファルコ あーしも降りる
Falco! Lemme off too!
‎ああ？
What?
‎（ドアが閉まる音）
‎しゃあねえ ２人で飲むか
Well dang,
guess the after-party's just us two.
I've got somewhere to be, too.
‎（キーウィ）ファルコ～
‎私も降ろしてほしいとこある
That so? Bunch of killjoys,
you, one and all.
‎あっそう
‎つきあいの悪い連中だぜ
David!
（レベッカ）
デイビッド！
No after-party today?
（デイビッド）
飲みに行かないのか？
（レベッカ）ジジババと
飲んでもつまんねーよ
Can't get drunk with those two boomers.
（デイビッド）俺が
いたって面白くないだろ
Can't promise I'll be any more fun.
Don't underestimate yourself!
（レベッカ）
んなこたねえよ
Hey… Wanna take a walk?
なあ ちっと歩こうぜ
Huh? Sure, I guess…
（デイビッド）
え？　ああ… いいよ
Yes!
（レベッカ）うっしゃ！
So… you doing okay?
‎（レベッカ）なあ 大丈夫かあ？
‎（デイビッド）何が？
What?
‎（レベッカ）今日のあれ 何？
What was that today?
‎（デイビッド）何って？
What was what?
‎（レベッカ）そういうの要らない
‎（デイビッド）何でもない
You know what I mean.
It was nothing.
This isn't the first time it's happened.
‎（レベッカ）
‎今日が初めてじゃないよな
You thought I didn't notice?
‎気付かれてないと思った？
Whatever.
‎（デイビッド）まあな
‎（レベッカ）女を見くびんなよ
A girl's intuition, you know?
What girl?
‎（デイビッド）女？
‎（レベッカ）ブッ殺すぞ
Shut up.
‎（２人の笑い声）
‎（レベッカ）
‎まっ あーしが そんだけ
You're the only one I watch
that closely, you know.
‎あんたを見てるってことなんよ
‎なあ デイビッド
Come on, David. What's wrong?
‎なんかあった？
Nothing.
‎（デイビッド）ないよ
‎（レベッカ）まだ隠す気？
I said cut the bull.
It's got nothing to do with you.
‎レベッカには関係ない
（レベッカ）
関係ねーことあるかよ
Like hell it doesn't.
I'm putting my life in your hands.
あんたに
命 預けてんだぜ
Sorry.
‎ごめん
‎（走る足音）
I was thinking…
‎（レベッカ）あのさ デイビッド
‎（デイビッド）ん？
Yeah?
‎（レベッカ）
‎インプラントは しばらく使うな
You should lay off
the implants for a while.
Don't worry. I've got your back!
‎あたしがカバーすっからさ！
You?
‎お前が？
I'm being serious.
‎マジで言ってんだけど
Remember the psycho
that flatlined my brother?
‎アニキを殺したサイバーサイコ野郎
‎覚えてる？
Yeah.
‎（デイビッド）ああ
‎（レベッカ）あんたは…
I don't… wanna see you end up like that.
‎あんなふうになっちゃ嫌だよ
Yeah.
‎ああ
‎あ…
‎（装着音）
‎ハッ…
They're still sending runners?
‎まだ探してるランナーがいるの？
‎（テレビ音声）
‎（ルーシー）んん？
‎（ホロ通信：キーウィ）
‎残ってるのはターゲットだけよ
‎情報どおりね
‎（解錠音）
‎開けた
‎侵入路 確保
Hm?
‎ん？　誰だ！
Who are you? W-What the…
‎な… 何を！
‎ああ… あっ ああっ！
‎（発砲音）
‎（キーウィ）
‎デイビッド もう‎殺(や)‎った？
‎中に もう１人残ってた
‎そっちに向かってる
‎マズい 部屋に入ってくる
‎ねえ 聞いてる？
‎（ユミコ）ひっ！
‎（箱が落ちた音）
Wait…
‎待って
‎あ…
‎（不気味な笑い声）
‎（発砲音）
‎（キーウィ）
‎ねえ 聞こえてる？ デイビッド
‎（デイビッド）‎ん… ああ
‎（キーウィ）
‎さっきから呼んでたのに
‎１人 そっちに戻ってったから
‎（デイビッド）‎処理した
‎すぐに出る
‎ハッ… デイビッド！
David!
‎（リパードク）目が覚めたか
Rise and shine.
‎（デイビッド）ドク…
Doc…
Symptoms settling down?
‎（リパードク）
‎少しは落ち着いたか？
Yeah…
‎（デイビッド）ああ
‎（リパードク）いつからだ？
‎（デイビッド）いつって？
When did it start?
What?
‎手の震え めまい 吐き気
‎兆候はあったろ？
Shaky hands, dizziness,
nausea, usual suspects.
A little while ago.
‎ああ… 少し前から
‎なんで すぐ言わなかった？
Why didn't you tell me?
Thought it was temporary.
‎一時的なもんだと
Looks like side-effects
are finally catching up with you.
‎とうとう お前にも副作用か
Of course, it's crazy enough
how you've been fine until now.
‎もっとも今まで平気だったのも
‎十分 異常だったがな
Why now?
‎なんで今さら
Lay off the chrome for a while.
‎しばらくはインプラントの起動を
‎控えるんだな
You're already one foot
in the psycho zone.
‎もはやサイバーサイコシスの
‎一歩手前さ
Then gimme stronger meds for it!
‎じゃあ もっと強い薬をくれよ！
‎おいおい
Shit. You ain't hearing me.
Or have you already lost your mind?
‎もうとっくにサイバーサイコシスに
‎なっちまってんのかあ？
Ain't no such miracle drug in exist…
‎そんな都合のいい薬がありゃ…
‎（ガタン！）
Think I came for jokes?
Take my fucking money…
‎いいから よこせよ
‎ゴチャゴチャ言ってねえで
‎あんたはカネだけ受け取ってろ！
and gimme the fucking meds!
（ノイズ音）
David!
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド！
‎（リパードクの苦しむ声）
‎（せき込み）
‎（リパードク）そら 最後の処方だ
There. Your last prescription. Nine times
standard dosage, good for nine days.
‎９倍のタンク９日分
‎エッジを越えるには十分な量だ
It'll send you straight over the edge
and right to hell.
‎地獄に一直線さ
I'm sorry. I won't let it happen again.
‎（デイビッド）
‎悪かったよ　二度としない
It's fine.
‎（リパードク）いいんだ
‎その薬を出すってことは
The fact that you need those meds means
you won't be coming back here anymore.
‎もう お前は二度と
‎ここには戻ってこない
A kid off the block pushing XBDs and now…
‎裏‎ＢＤ(ビーディー)‎売らしてたガキが
‎ここまで変わるとはな
Go be a legend or
whatever the fuck you punks do.
‎せいぜい伝説ってやつにでもなりな
‎ありきたりのな
‎（ドアが閉まる音）
Just another tale for the next dreamer…
‎（リパードク）語り継いでやるよ
‎（ルーシー）デイビッド 待って
David! Wait! What was that?
‎さっきのは何？
Don't tell the guys.
‎みんなには言うな
I don't understand.
‎どういうこと？
‎ねえ！
Hey!
Your body, your mind…
They have limits, David. You knew that.
‎インプラントを入れ過ぎたら
‎いつか限界はくる
Normal meds don't do it for you anymore.
‎もう普通の抑制剤じゃ抑えられない
Isn't it time to call quits?
‎もういいでしょ？
I can't watch you do this to yourself.
Scale back your cyberware…
‎変わってくあんたを見てられない
‎インプラントなんか外して
I can't do that.
‎（デイビッド）それはできないよ
Why not?
‎なんで？
Mom and Maine…
They all left me something to do.
‎母さんもメインも
‎何か俺に託して死んだ
But I haven't done nothing yet.
‎俺は まだ何もできてない
But you can't keep going on like this…
‎そんなこと…
‎だって それ以上…
I'll be fine.
‎（デイビッド）俺なら大丈夫だよ
How could you say that?
Do you really think you're special?
‎（ルーシー）どうして？
‎自分は特別だと本当に思ってるの？
‎（デイビッド）
‎サンデヴィスタンに耐えられたんだ
I withstood the Sandevistan.
I'm not normal.
‎普通ってことはないだろ
So you're a little more sturdy than
everyone else. But you're still human.
‎人よりいくらか
‎耐性が強いかもしれない
‎でも あなたは普通の人よ
‎（ダン！）
I shot a woman.
‎（デイビッド）女の人を撃った
Huh?
‎え？
She was around the same age as my mom.
‎（デイビッド）
‎母さんと同じくらいの年だ
She also had a son like me.
‎俺ぐらいの子供もいた
A harmless bystander. A normal person.
‎犯罪者でもない普通の人だった
I don't know how many I've killed anymore.
‎もう 今まで何人殺したかも
‎分からない
It doesn't even make me pause anymore.
‎人を殺しても何とも思わないんだ
Maybe I really am going crazy.
‎俺は もう
‎狂ってるのかもしれない
David…
‎デイビッド…
I ain't normal.
Like you said before, I'm different.
‎（デイビッド）普通なんかじゃない
‎もう君とは違うんだ
You're not.
‎（ルーシー）違わないわ
‎（デイビッド）違うさ
I am!
You're not.
‎（ルーシー）違わないわ
‎（デイビッド）君には無理なんだ
You wouldn't understand.
‎（ルーシー）え？
You left the crew after Maine died.
‎（デイビッド）メインが死んでから
‎チームに加わらなかっただろ？
That's because…
‎（ルーシー）それは…
I'm not blaming you.
‎（デイビッド）それでよかったんだ
‎（ルーシー）どうして？
Why not?
You shouldn't have to live this life.
‎（デイビッド）
‎君は 俺みたいになるな
No, David. That's not what I…
‎（ルーシー）
‎違うの デイビッド　私は…
Then you'll come back?
‎（デイビッド）
‎なら チームに戻れるかい？
Let's go back to the way things were,
working together.
‎前みたいにさ 一緒にやろうぜ
I can't right now.
Wait for me a little while longer.
‎今は無理　もう少しだけ待って
‎（デイビッド）なぜ？
What for?
There's something I need to do first.
‎（ルーシー）どうしても
‎やらなきゃいけないことがあるの
Like what?
‎（デイビッド）それ何なの？
‎（ルーシー）詳しくは言えない
I can't say.
Why?
‎（デイビッド）なんで？
‎（ルーシー）ごめん
Sorry.
Because you don't trust me.
‎（デイビッド）
‎俺にも言えないってこと？
I'm sorry.
‎（ルーシー）ごめんなさい
Okay. I'll stop asking you about it.
‎（デイビッド）
‎分かった　もう聞かないよ
Okay.
‎（ルーシー）ええ
‎（デイビッド）
‎俺たち 別々の道を行くほうが
Maybe we should go our separate ways.
‎いいのかもしれないな
No! That's not true David.
‎違う！
‎そうじゃないの デイビッド
I'm sorry, David. I have to go.
‎ごめん デイビッド
‎私 行かなきゃ…
Huh? Where?
‎え… どこへ？
I have to go…
（ルーシー）行かなきゃ
Okay.
（デイビッド）分かった
（ルーシー）帰ったら
ちゃんと話そう
We'll talk when I get home.
Wait for me.
‎だから待ってて
The same ID as the runner from before.
‎（ルーシー）
‎この間のランナーＩＤと同じ
There you are…
‎見つけたわ
‎（ワイヤーを引く音）
‎（ノイズ音）
‎フン
‎あ！
‎ぐっ！
あ… ああ…
（苦しむ声）
ぐぐっ…
Didn't think it would be so easy.
‎（ファラデー）
‎こんなに あっさり手に入るとはな
‎（ブツッ！）
This is our passport into Arasaka.
‎この手土産が
‎アラサカへのパスポートとなる
Excellent job, Kiwi.
‎よくやった キーウィ
♪～
～♪